<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Assignment_1</string>
    <string name="android">Android operating system is the largest installed base among various mobile platforms across the globe. Hundreds of millions of mobile devices are powered by Android in more than 190 countries of the world. It conquered around 71% of the global market share by the end of 2021, and this trend is growing bigger every other day. The company named Open Handset Alliance developed Android for the first time that is based on the modified version of the Linux kernel and other open-source software. Google sponsored the project at initial stages and in the year 2005, it acquired the whole company. In September 2008, the first Android-powered device was launched in the market. Android dominates the mobile OS industry because of the long list of features it provides. It’s user-friendly, has huge community support, provides a greater extent of customization, and a large number of companies build Android-compatible smartphones. As a result, the market observes a sharp increase in the demand for developing Android mobile applications, and with that companies need smart developers with the right skill set. At first, the purpose of Android was thought of as a mobile operating system. However, with the advancement of code libraries and its popularity among developers of the divergent domain, Android becomes an absolute set of software for all devices like tablets, wearables, set-top boxes, smart TVs, notebooks, etc.</string>
    <string name="web">Web development is the work involved in developing a website for the Internet (World Wide Web) or an intranet (a private network).[1] Web development can range from developing a simple single static page of plain text to complex web applications, electronic businesses, and social network services. A more comprehensive list of tasks to which Web development commonly refers, may include Web engineering, Web design, Web content development, client liaison, client-side/server-side scripting, Web server and network security configuration, and e-commerce development.
Among Web professionals, "Web development" usually refers to the main non-design aspects of building Web sites: writing markup and coding.[2] Web development may use content management systems (CMS) to make content changes easier and available with basic technical skills.</string>
    <string name="dsa">A data structure is defined as a particular way of storing and organizing data in our devices to use the data efficiently and effectively. The main idea behind using data structures is to minimize the time and space complexities. An efficient data structure takes minimum memory space and requires minimum time to execute the data</string>
    <string name="ai">Artificial intelligence (AI) is a field of computer science that aims to make machines perform human-like functions, such as learning, reasoning, and problem-solving. AI relies on technologies such as **deep learning** and **natural language processing**, which enable computers to process large amounts of data and identify patterns. Machine learning is a branch of AI that focuses on training machines to learn and think on their own using complex algorithms. Machine learning platforms are applications that use machine learning to provide data analysis, prediction, and categorization services¹.

There are many technologies used in AI such as **Basis Technology**, **Expert System**, **Coveo**, **Indico**, **Knime**, **Lexalytics**, **Linguamatics**, **Mindbreeze**, **Sinequa**, **Stratifyd** and **Synapsify**⁴.

AI applications include advanced web search engines (e.g., Google Search), recommendation systems (used by YouTube, Amazon, and Netflix), understanding human speech (such as Siri and Alexa), self-driving cars (e.g., Waymo), generative or creative tools (ChatGPT and AI art), and competing at the highest level in strategic games (such as chess and Go)⁵.

I hope this helps!

Source: Conversation with Bing, 30/7/2023
(1) What Is Artificial Intelligence Technology and How Is It Used?. https://bluedragondigitalmarketing.com/what-is-artificial-intelligence-technology-how-is-it-used/.
(2) Top 15 Hot Artificial Intelligence Technologies - Edureka. https://www.edureka.co/blog/top-15-hot-artificial-intelligence-technologies/.
(3) Artificial intelligence - Wikipedia. https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Artificial_intelligence.
(4) Artificial Intelligence Technology | 18 Useful Technologies Used in AI. https://www.educba.com/artificial-intelligence-technology/.
(5) Artificial intelligence (AI) | Definition, Examples, Types .... https://www.britannica.com/technology/artificial-intelligence.
(6) The 5 Biggest Artificial Intelligence (AI) Trends In 2023 - Forbes. https://www.forbes.com/sites/bernardmarr/2022/10/10/the-5-biggest-artificial-intelligence-ai-trends-in-2023/.</string>
<string name="block">A blockchain is a distributed ledger with growing lists of records (blocks) that are securely linked together via cryptographic hashes.[1][2][3][4] Each block contains a cryptographic hash of the previous block, a timestamp, and transaction data (generally represented as a Merkle tree, where data nodes are represented by leaves). Since each block contains information about the previous block, they effectively form a chain (compare linked list data structure),
    with each additional block linking to the ones before it. Consequently, blockchain transactions are irreversible in that, once they are recorded, the data in any given block cannot be altered retroactively without altering all subsequent blocks.</string>
<string name="ml">Machine learning is an umbrella term for solving problems for which development of algorithms by human programmers would be cost-prohibitive, and instead the problems are solved by helping machines discover their own algorithms, without needing to be explicitly told what to do by any human-developed algorithms. Recently, generative artificial neural networks have been able to surpass results of many previous approaches. Machine learning approaches have been applied to large language models, computer vision, speech recognition,
    email filtering, agriculture and medicine, where it is too costly to develop algorithms to perform the needed tasks.Deep learning is part of a broader family of machine learning methods, which is based on artificial neural networks with representation learning. The adjective "deep" in deep learning refers to the use of multiple layers in the network. Methods used can be either supervised, semi-supervised or unsupervised.</string>
</resources>